Hey guys, welcome to another video, so let me show you another kind of persistence that will
be also commonly used payer detectors, so when they are initiating the tactics persistence
on the canism, so the name is start up folder persistence, so there are two kind of folders
you can choose for the post and this for a current user and this from all user, so my current
user will be the usernamely user and if I want to this directory in my visual machine,
you can find the directory here, so the folder is empty, so if you push any files inside
this directory it will be get automatically initiated, so once the system get turned on
ok, so once the user logged on onto the machine the malware will be get automatically executed
without any interaction from any users, so this was executed by the Windows operating system
automatically, so let us let us see another directory, so this is one of the powerful
directory, we can choose for a persistence canism, see program rate of Microsoft Windows
start up menu program and start up, so let me go to the directory, so here you can find
this folder is also empty, so if you have any malicious files you can, you can just pull
the files inside this directory, it will be get automatically executed once the machine
has been turned on, ok, let I will show you my call and I will show you what I did,
I just created a payload using the port 8765 and with the start of folder.exe, also
I just opened a listener, so now I am going to download this start up folder.exe and
I will put that file in my Windows machine, the start of folder and I will say that it
was executing automatically or not, let me download this and copy this file, so you know
how to work on the command prompt, so if you get a reverse connection from any of an organization
or any of a machine, see users, user and updated roaming Microsoft Windows, update roaming
Microsoft Windows, here you can find the start up menu and programs start up, ok, let I will
push the file inside this directory and I will be restarting my machine, and I will execute
around here, let us start our multi handler listener and we will wait for the machine to
be turned on, the device was ready, let me login to the device, I will just ignore this
I will wait for few more minutes, sorry few more seconds, ok see it was automatically asking
where you need to execute this file or not if I run this file, so I got a reverse connection
from I got a reverse connection from the specific device, so you can you can play around
the device whatever you want like yesterday, I will execute this, ok, so I do not want
the session anymore, so let us hop of this video because I hope you have a great understanding
about the start up folder, the next video we are going to see an advanced method, most
of the detectors will be using that, because the start up folder, and registry, processing
it was asking whether you need to execute this file or not, it is just triggered a
prompt right, you need to run the file or not, but the next method it will not going to
ask whether you need to run this file or not, it will be automatically running your payload
without any interaction, ok, so let us hop of and we will connect to you guys in the next
video, see you, bye bye.